Thank you so much for acknowledging Antifa
and for directing your administration to treat them
as domestic terrorists.
It's going to be really challenging
because how they organize is that they are decentralized,
autonomous, and they operate on deception.
And we're still to this day told that they don't exist,
that it's a figment of our imagination.
I think the DOJ could look at federal conspiracy charges.
The state of California in San Diego County last year broke
up an Antifa cell in San Diego.
And I think maybe perhaps the State Department should
designate Antifa, its international arm,
as a foreign terrorist organization, FTO.
So thank you so much for this invitation, Mr. President.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, Andy.
Great. That's a rough time you had, huh?
So the chokeout was almost the end, you felt?
Yeah, that was my only near-death experience
in my life, and I'm quite shaken when I think about it now.
It really feels unbelievable to me that on the streets
of America that this type of violence against citizens.
So routine and accepted and cheered on by people.
Although, you know, in the immediate aftermath
of Mr. Kirk's assassination, we saw again that type
of depravity play out on quite large swaths of the left.
So there's a.